{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888803925","data":{"timestamp":" 946888803924"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARAKA"," userResponse":" BARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888804602","data":{"timestamp":" 946888804601"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888804815","data":{"timestamp":" 946888804815"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888805392","data":{"timestamp":" 946888805392"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888806011","data":{"timestamp":" 946888806010"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATU"," userResponse":" MATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888806165","data":{"timestamp":" 946888806165"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888806924","data":{"timestamp":" 946888806923"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888809415","data":{"timestamp":" 946888809415"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888810062","data":{"timestamp":" 946888810061"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888810397","data":{"timestamp":" 946888810396"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888810901","data":{"timestamp":" 946888810900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUSA"," userResponse":" MUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888811777","data":{"timestamp":" 946888811777"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888812453","data":{"timestamp":" 946888812452"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWILI"," userResponse":" MAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888814938","data":{"timestamp":" 946888814937"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARAKA"," userResponse":" BARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888815653","data":{"timestamp":" 946888815652"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEBAKI"," userResponse":" AMEBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888815831","data":{"timestamp":" 946888815831"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888816427","data":{"timestamp":" 946888816426"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888817074","data":{"timestamp":" 946888817074"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888817761","data":{"timestamp":" 946888817760"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888822604","data":{"timestamp":" 946888822603"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ____"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____"," userResponse":" ____"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888828402","data":{"timestamp":" 946888828402"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARAKA"," userResponse":" BARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888829080","data":{"timestamp":" 946888829078"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888829297","data":{"timestamp":" 946888829297"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888829873","data":{"timestamp":" 946888829873"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888830492","data":{"timestamp":" 946888830491"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATU"," userResponse":" MATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888830656","data":{"timestamp":" 946888830656"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::math.word_problem_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888831081","data":{"timestamp":" 946888831081"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888831151","data":{"timestamp":" 946888831151"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888836872","data":{"timestamp":" 946888836871"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888842471","data":{"timestamp":" 946888842471"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" fbb0afed-034c-41eb-9bc2-8b52f748f021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__math.word_problem_4__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baraka alikuwa na magari matatu ya kuchezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888852543","data":{"timestamp":" 946888852543"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888853299","data":{"timestamp":" 946888853298"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888853501","data":{"timestamp":" 946888853500"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888854266","data":{"timestamp":" 946888854266"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888857686","data":{"timestamp":" 946888857685"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEPANDWA"," userResponse":" IMEPANDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888858456","data":{"timestamp":" 946888858455"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888862696","data":{"timestamp":" 946888862695"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIENDA"," userResponse":" UKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888863620","data":{"timestamp":" 946888863620"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888864445","data":{"timestamp":" 946888864444"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888868090","data":{"timestamp":" 946888868090"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAHARIBU"," userResponse":" UTAHARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888868952","data":{"timestamp":" 946888868951"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888872921","data":{"timestamp":" 946888872920"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mazingira mazuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZINGIRA"," userResponse":" MAZINGIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888873864","data":{"timestamp":" 946888873863"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mazingira mazuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888877860","data":{"timestamp":" 946888877859"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yamepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMEPANDWA"," userResponse":" YAMEPANDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888879084","data":{"timestamp":" 946888879083"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yamepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888882735","data":{"timestamp":" 946888882734"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIENDA"," userResponse":" UKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888883661","data":{"timestamp":" 946888883661"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888884486","data":{"timestamp":" 946888884486"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888888107","data":{"timestamp":" 946888888107"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAHARIBU"," userResponse":" UTAHARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888888972","data":{"timestamp":" 946888888971"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888892129","data":{"timestamp":" 946888892128"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888892211","data":{"timestamp":" 946888892211"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888896993","data":{"timestamp":" 946888896992"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888904698","data":{"timestamp":" 946888904698"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888910043","data":{"timestamp":" 946888910043"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" ec825de3-f818-4a04-bf3a-e2fa4600e262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_6"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:100_1000__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888915654","data":{"timestamp":" 946888915653"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 68678190-e404-4650-a1da-1c46bb5ef286"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_100_1000__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 1000"," problemName":" 1000"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:100_1000__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888931063","data":{"timestamp":" 946888931063"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 68678190-e404-4650-a1da-1c46bb5ef286"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_100_1000__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 1000"," problemName":" 1000"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:100_1000__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888933349","data":{"timestamp":" 946888933348"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 68678190-e404-4650-a1da-1c46bb5ef286"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_100_1000__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 1000"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888933483","data":{"timestamp":" 946888933483"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 68678190-e404-4650-a1da-1c46bb5ef286"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_100_1000__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 1000"," problemName":" 1000"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888938635","data":{"timestamp":" 946888938635"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 68678190-e404-4650-a1da-1c46bb5ef286"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_100_1000__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 1000"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888944124","data":{"timestamp":" 946888944123"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 68678190-e404-4650-a1da-1c46bb5ef286"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_100_1000__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 1000"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888949400","data":{"timestamp":" 946888949400"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 68678190-e404-4650-a1da-1c46bb5ef286"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_100_1000__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 1000"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888961948","data":{"timestamp":" 946888961948"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888963205","data":{"timestamp":" 946888963204"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888964168","data":{"timestamp":" 946888964168"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888965898","data":{"timestamp":" 946888965898"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABINI"," userResponse":" SABINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888966515","data":{"timestamp":" 946888966515"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888968013","data":{"timestamp":" 946888968012"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888971283","data":{"timestamp":" 946888971282"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888972614","data":{"timestamp":" 946888972614"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888974234","data":{"timestamp":" 946888974234"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888975714","data":{"timestamp":" 946888975714"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888977329","data":{"timestamp":" 946888977329"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888978574","data":{"timestamp":" 946888978574"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sabini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888980933","data":{"timestamp":" 946888980932"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888982330","data":{"timestamp":" 946888982330"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888983400","data":{"timestamp":" 946888983400"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888985279","data":{"timestamp":" 946888985279"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITINI"," userResponse":" SITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888985970","data":{"timestamp":" 946888985970"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888987605","data":{"timestamp":" 946888987605"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888989059","data":{"timestamp":" 946888989059"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888991089","data":{"timestamp":" 946888991089"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888993903","data":{"timestamp":" 946888993903"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888995435","data":{"timestamp":" 946888995434"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888997253","data":{"timestamp":" 946888997253"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946888998884","data":{"timestamp":" 946888998883"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na sitini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889001220","data":{"timestamp":" 946889001220"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889002509","data":{"timestamp":" 946889002509"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889003559","data":{"timestamp":" 946889003559"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889005457","data":{"timestamp":" 946889005457"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMSINI"," userResponse":" HAMSINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889006486","data":{"timestamp":" 946889006485"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889008105","data":{"timestamp":" 946889008105"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889011018","data":{"timestamp":" 946889011017"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889012337","data":{"timestamp":" 946889012337"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889014256","data":{"timestamp":" 946889014256"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889016165","data":{"timestamp":" 946889016165"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMSINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889017968","data":{"timestamp":" 946889017968"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889019212","data":{"timestamp":" 946889019212"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na hamsini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889021549","data":{"timestamp":" 946889021549"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889022818","data":{"timestamp":" 946889022818"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889023869","data":{"timestamp":" 946889023869"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889025819","data":{"timestamp":" 946889025819"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AROBAINI"," userResponse":" AROBAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889026745","data":{"timestamp":" 946889026745"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889028372","data":{"timestamp":" 946889028372"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889029882","data":{"timestamp":" 946889029882"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889031382","data":{"timestamp":" 946889031382"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889032604","data":{"timestamp":" 946889032604"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889034331","data":{"timestamp":" 946889034331"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889036168","data":{"timestamp":" 946889036168"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AROBAINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889041076","data":{"timestamp":" 946889041075"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889042343","data":{"timestamp":" 946889042342"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na arobaini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889044700","data":{"timestamp":" 946889044700"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889046096","data":{"timestamp":" 946889046096"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889047125","data":{"timestamp":" 946889047125"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889048916","data":{"timestamp":" 946889048916"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" THELATHINI"," userResponse":" THELATHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889049945","data":{"timestamp":" 946889049945"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889051565","data":{"timestamp":" 946889051565"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889053785","data":{"timestamp":" 946889053785"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889055219","data":{"timestamp":" 946889055218"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889057353","data":{"timestamp":" 946889057353"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889059158","data":{"timestamp":" 946889059158"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" THELATHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889060966","data":{"timestamp":" 946889060965"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889062097","data":{"timestamp":" 946889062097"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na thelathini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889064415","data":{"timestamp":" 946889064415"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889065701","data":{"timestamp":" 946889065701"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889066731","data":{"timestamp":" 946889066731"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889068473","data":{"timestamp":" 946889068473"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHIRINI"," userResponse":" ISHIRINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889069715","data":{"timestamp":" 946889069714"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889071356","data":{"timestamp":" 946889071355"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889072989","data":{"timestamp":" 946889072988"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889077980","data":{"timestamp":" 946889077980"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889078750","data":{"timestamp":" 946889078750"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889079070","data":{"timestamp":" 946889079070"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889084596","data":{"timestamp":" 946889084596"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISHIRINI"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889086899","data":{"timestamp":" 946889086899"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHIRINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889089498","data":{"timestamp":" 946889089498"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889092237","data":{"timestamp":" 946889092236"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na ishirini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889094565","data":{"timestamp":" 946889094565"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889095864","data":{"timestamp":" 946889095864"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889096917","data":{"timestamp":" 946889096917"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889098444","data":{"timestamp":" 946889098444"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889099039","data":{"timestamp":" 946889099039"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889100650","data":{"timestamp":" 946889100650"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889102546","data":{"timestamp":" 946889102546"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889103749","data":{"timestamp":" 946889103749"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889107055","data":{"timestamp":" 946889107055"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889110102","data":{"timestamp":" 946889110102"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889111190","data":{"timestamp":" 946889111189"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889114378","data":{"timestamp":" 946889114378"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na kumi na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889116706","data":{"timestamp":" 946889116706"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889117979","data":{"timestamp":" 946889117979"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889119009","data":{"timestamp":" 946889119009"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889120376","data":{"timestamp":" 946889120376"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889125660","data":{"timestamp":" 946889125660"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889126860","data":{"timestamp":" 946889126860"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889129078","data":{"timestamp":" 946889129078"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889130706","data":{"timestamp":" 946889130706"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889133018","data":{"timestamp":" 946889133018"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889133357","data":{"timestamp":" 946889133356"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889134717","data":{"timestamp":" 946889134717"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889136561","data":{"timestamp":" 946889136561"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" THEMANINI"," userResponse":" THEMANINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889137274","data":{"timestamp":" 946889137274"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889138906","data":{"timestamp":" 946889138906"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889141747","data":{"timestamp":" 946889141746"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889143983","data":{"timestamp":" 946889143983"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889146400","data":{"timestamp":" 946889146400"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889147957","data":{"timestamp":" 946889147957"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" THEMANINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889149685","data":{"timestamp":" 946889149685"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889151017","data":{"timestamp":" 946889151017"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889153036","data":{"timestamp":" 946889153036"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889153193","data":{"timestamp":" 946889153193"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889160370","data":{"timestamp":" 946889160370"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889165740","data":{"timestamp":" 946889165740"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889171221","data":{"timestamp":" 946889171221"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889178451","data":{"timestamp":" 946889178450"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889183846","data":{"timestamp":" 946889183846"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889189088","data":{"timestamp":" 946889189088"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889194509","data":{"timestamp":" 946889194509"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" a03245b4-96bf-47c2-b3de-353a12509cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..900.TD_OFF10_DES.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia saba na themanini na tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889207912","data":{"timestamp":" 946889207912"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_112_112-566-675"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 112"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889219771","data":{"timestamp":" 946889219771"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_158_878-112-158"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 158"," userResponse":" 158"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889232610","data":{"timestamp":" 946889232610"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_247_878-247-566"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 247"," userResponse":" 247"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889245423","data":{"timestamp":" 946889245423"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_331_938-112-331"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 331"," userResponse":" 331"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889256917","data":{"timestamp":" 946889256917"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_446_247-158-446"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 446"," userResponse":" 446"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889268896","data":{"timestamp":" 946889268896"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_566_331-878-566"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 566"," userResponse":" 566"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889280858","data":{"timestamp":" 946889280858"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_675_675-781-878"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 675"," userResponse":" 675"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889293220","data":{"timestamp":" 946889293220"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_781_781-566-938"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 781"," userResponse":" 781"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889305676","data":{"timestamp":" 946889305676"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_878_566-878-247"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 878"," userResponse":" 878"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889320414","data":{"timestamp":" 946889320414"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_938_566-938-331"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 938"," userResponse":" 938"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889330319","data":{"timestamp":" 946889330317"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_938_566-938-331"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889335139","data":{"timestamp":" 946889335139"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_938_566-938-331"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889340340","data":{"timestamp":" 946889340339"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_938_566-938-331"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889345405","data":{"timestamp":" 946889345404"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 79e68494-c106-41c6-8adc-b5027ce3b7a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.s2s.AV.mc.68"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_938_566-938-331"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889355834","data":{"timestamp":" 946889355834"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889356923","data":{"timestamp":" 946889356923"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHESABU"," userResponse":" KUHESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889357845","data":{"timestamp":" 946889357844"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBA"," userResponse":" NAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889361120","data":{"timestamp":" 946889361119"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889361623","data":{"timestamp":" 946889361623"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889362253","data":{"timestamp":" 946889362253"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889365312","data":{"timestamp":" 946889365311"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889366120","data":{"timestamp":" 946889366120"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889366525","data":{"timestamp":" 946889366524"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889367267","data":{"timestamp":" 946889367267"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889370429","data":{"timestamp":" 946889370428"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889371061","data":{"timestamp":" 946889371060"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889371603","data":{"timestamp":" 946889371603"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889374667","data":{"timestamp":" 946889374666"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889374756","data":{"timestamp":" 946889374756"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889381181","data":{"timestamp":" 946889381181"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" e2976797-909f-4b46-a29b-51c418d9b631"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889390246","data":{"timestamp":" 946889390246"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 2a6522a4-70a0-4300-b284-de0e687a8f73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889390468","data":{"timestamp":" 946889390468"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 2a6522a4-70a0-4300-b284-de0e687a8f73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889390484","data":{"timestamp":" 946889390484"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 2a6522a4-70a0-4300-b284-de0e687a8f73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889390563","data":{"timestamp":" 946889390562"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 2a6522a4-70a0-4300-b284-de0e687a8f73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889395930","data":{"timestamp":" 946889395930"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 2a6522a4-70a0-4300-b284-de0e687a8f73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889407866","data":{"timestamp":" 946889407866"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889409063","data":{"timestamp":" 946889409063"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889411010","data":{"timestamp":" 946889411010"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889412274","data":{"timestamp":" 946889412274"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889414598","data":{"timestamp":" 946889414598"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889415985","data":{"timestamp":" 946889415985"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889417828","data":{"timestamp":" 946889417828"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889419803","data":{"timestamp":" 946889419802"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889422166","data":{"timestamp":" 946889422166"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889423494","data":{"timestamp":" 946889423493"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889425334","data":{"timestamp":" 946889425334"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889426562","data":{"timestamp":" 946889426562"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889428880","data":{"timestamp":" 946889428880"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889430078","data":{"timestamp":" 946889430078"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889431926","data":{"timestamp":" 946889431926"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889433118","data":{"timestamp":" 946889433118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889435466","data":{"timestamp":" 946889435466"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889436707","data":{"timestamp":" 946889436707"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889437916","data":{"timestamp":" 946889437916"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889439820","data":{"timestamp":" 946889439820"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889441534","data":{"timestamp":" 946889441533"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889443849","data":{"timestamp":" 946889443849"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889445234","data":{"timestamp":" 946889445234"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889447009","data":{"timestamp":" 946889447009"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889448183","data":{"timestamp":" 946889448183"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889450510","data":{"timestamp":" 946889450510"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889451821","data":{"timestamp":" 946889451821"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889454882","data":{"timestamp":" 946889454881"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889456187","data":{"timestamp":" 946889456187"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889458536","data":{"timestamp":" 946889458536"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889459800","data":{"timestamp":" 946889459800"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889461665","data":{"timestamp":" 946889461665"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889463078","data":{"timestamp":" 946889463078"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889465395","data":{"timestamp":" 946889465395"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889466609","data":{"timestamp":" 946889466608"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889468591","data":{"timestamp":" 946889468591"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889470493","data":{"timestamp":" 946889470492"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889472766","data":{"timestamp":" 946889472766"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELFU"," userResponse":" ELFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889474317","data":{"timestamp":" 946889474317"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889476454","data":{"timestamp":" 946889476454"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889478022","data":{"timestamp":" 946889478021"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889480047","data":{"timestamp":" 946889480046"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889480211","data":{"timestamp":" 946889480211"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889484720","data":{"timestamp":" 946889484720"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889489901","data":{"timestamp":" 946889489901"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889495136","data":{"timestamp":" 946889495136"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 5654be30-5d46-4c11-98c9-dc7e7f6d27d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889506369","data":{"timestamp":" 946889506368"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" b5f2f925-fbe1-4d4b-ae66-33c8a54ab54c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.44"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889506389","data":{"timestamp":" 946889506389"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" b5f2f925-fbe1-4d4b-ae66-33c8a54ab54c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.44"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889506537","data":{"timestamp":" 946889506537"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" b5f2f925-fbe1-4d4b-ae66-33c8a54ab54c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.44"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889511501","data":{"timestamp":" 946889511501"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" b5f2f925-fbe1-4d4b-ae66-33c8a54ab54c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFF100_INC.44"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889520677","data":{"timestamp":" 946889520677"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 3b73f758-cd0a-4f01-9c4d-5e946578d512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889520909","data":{"timestamp":" 946889520909"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 3b73f758-cd0a-4f01-9c4d-5e946578d512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889521888","data":{"timestamp":" 946889521886"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 3b73f758-cd0a-4f01-9c4d-5e946578d512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889523170","data":{"timestamp":" 946889523170"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 3b73f758-cd0a-4f01-9c4d-5e946578d512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889523921","data":{"timestamp":" 946889523921"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 3b73f758-cd0a-4f01-9c4d-5e946578d512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889523972","data":{"timestamp":" 946889523972"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 3b73f758-cd0a-4f01-9c4d-5e946578d512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889528103","data":{"timestamp":" 946889528102"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 3b73f758-cd0a-4f01-9c4d-5e946578d512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889537887","data":{"timestamp":" 946889537886"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_100_400-900-100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 100"," userResponse":" 100"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889543733","data":{"timestamp":" 946889543733"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_200_800-200-700"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 200"," userResponse":" 200"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889549264","data":{"timestamp":" 946889549263"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_300_300-1000-700"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889554914","data":{"timestamp":" 946889554914"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_400_400-700-300"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889560581","data":{"timestamp":" 946889560581"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_500_900-500-300"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 500"," userResponse":" 500"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889569352","data":{"timestamp":" 946889569352"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_600_600-200-300"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 600"," userResponse":" 600"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889578475","data":{"timestamp":" 946889578475"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_700_300-700-500"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 700"," userResponse":" 700"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889583785","data":{"timestamp":" 946889583785"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_800_800-200-500"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 800"," userResponse":" 800"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889590712","data":{"timestamp":" 946889590712"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_900_900-300-500"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 900"," userResponse":" 900"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889597384","data":{"timestamp":" 946889597383"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1000_1000-300-700"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1000"," userResponse":" 1000"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889605167","data":{"timestamp":" 946889605167"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1000_1000-300-700"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889610396","data":{"timestamp":" 946889610395"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 09866bf9-4a29-4ba4-8bf5-2e84ecbcafa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.100.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.71"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1000_1000-300-700"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889619222","data":{"timestamp":" 946889619222"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889619450","data":{"timestamp":" 946889619449"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889620423","data":{"timestamp":" 946889620423"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889621702","data":{"timestamp":" 946889621701"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889624723","data":{"timestamp":" 946889624722"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889625589","data":{"timestamp":" 946889625589"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889625915","data":{"timestamp":" 946889625914"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889627160","data":{"timestamp":" 946889627160"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889630766","data":{"timestamp":" 946889630766"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889631757","data":{"timestamp":" 946889631757"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889632017","data":{"timestamp":" 946889632017"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889632973","data":{"timestamp":" 946889632972"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889635906","data":{"timestamp":" 946889635902"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889636947","data":{"timestamp":" 946889636947"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889637431","data":{"timestamp":" 946889637430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889642004","data":{"timestamp":" 946889642003"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889642149","data":{"timestamp":" 946889642149"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889663080","data":{"timestamp":" 946889663080"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 7ce8da19-2580-4d26-9e77-4682c54223e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:100..1000.by.100.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889684128","data":{"timestamp":" 946889684128"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_1000_454_673"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:100..1000.by.100.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889690751","data":{"timestamp":" 946889690751"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_900_792_160"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:100..1000.by.100.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889694760","data":{"timestamp":" 946889694759"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_900_792_160"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889699761","data":{"timestamp":" 946889699760"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_900_792_160"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889705853","data":{"timestamp":" 946889705852"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_900_792_160"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889710934","data":{"timestamp":" 946889710934"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_900_792_160"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:100..1000.by.100.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889716749","data":{"timestamp":" 946889716748"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_900_792_160"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889721836","data":{"timestamp":" 946889721836"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_900_792_160"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889727002","data":{"timestamp":" 946889727002"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_900_792_160"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889732518","data":{"timestamp":" 946889732518"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 6ad72a19-05cd-4a34-93f7-af86aa3f0137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_100..1000.by.100.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_900_792_160"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889750141","data":{"timestamp":" 946889750141"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889752691","data":{"timestamp":" 946889752691"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889752966","data":{"timestamp":" 946889752966"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889767182","data":{"timestamp":" 946889767182"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_553"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889770973","data":{"timestamp":" 946889770972"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_553"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889774540","data":{"timestamp":" 946889774540"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_553"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889782639","data":{"timestamp":" 946889782639"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_553"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889796248","data":{"timestamp":" 946889796248"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_989"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889800394","data":{"timestamp":" 946889800394"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_989"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889803261","data":{"timestamp":" 946889803261"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_989"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889818825","data":{"timestamp":" 946889818824"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_344"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889822905","data":{"timestamp":" 946889822905"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_344"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889826465","data":{"timestamp":" 946889826465"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_344"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889838659","data":{"timestamp":" 946889838659"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_963"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889842936","data":{"timestamp":" 946889842935"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_963"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889847930","data":{"timestamp":" 946889847929"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_963"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889861470","data":{"timestamp":" 946889861470"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889867989","data":{"timestamp":" 946889867988"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889871700","data":{"timestamp":" 946889871700"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889877161","data":{"timestamp":" 946889877161"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889878917","data":{"timestamp":" 946889878917"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889890573","data":{"timestamp":" 946889890573"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_263"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889892437","data":{"timestamp":" 946889892437"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_263"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889898020","data":{"timestamp":" 946889898020"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_263"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889900229","data":{"timestamp":" 946889900229"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_263"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889901788","data":{"timestamp":" 946889901787"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_263"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889905418","data":{"timestamp":" 946889905418"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_263"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889913003","data":{"timestamp":" 946889913003"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_263"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889924949","data":{"timestamp":" 946889924949"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_263"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889937383","data":{"timestamp":" 946889937383"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_656"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889941388","data":{"timestamp":" 946889941388"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_656"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889944434","data":{"timestamp":" 946889944434"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_656"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889950121","data":{"timestamp":" 946889950121"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_656"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889961996","data":{"timestamp":" 946889961996"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_892"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889964416","data":{"timestamp":" 946889964416"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_892"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889967933","data":{"timestamp":" 946889967933"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_892"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889980199","data":{"timestamp":" 946889980199"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_974"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889986892","data":{"timestamp":" 946889986891"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_974"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889994267","data":{"timestamp":" 946889994267"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_974"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946889999238","data":{"timestamp":" 946889999238"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_974"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890012713","data":{"timestamp":" 946890012712"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890016984","data":{"timestamp":" 946890016984"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890020668","data":{"timestamp":" 946890020667"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-3D.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890032753","data":{"timestamp":" 946890032751"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890037548","data":{"timestamp":" 946890037547"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890042424","data":{"timestamp":" 946890042423"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890048073","data":{"timestamp":" 946890048072"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..1000.TD_OFF100_DES.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890055498","data":{"timestamp":" 946890055498"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890060709","data":{"timestamp":" 946890060709"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890065689","data":{"timestamp":" 946890065689"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890071328","data":{"timestamp":" 946890071327"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 72560948-edbe-4e46-a26e-79b0cbbbc8d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-3D.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_238"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890118355","data":{"timestamp":" 946890118355"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_126_485-126-317"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 126"," userResponse":" 126"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890130061","data":{"timestamp":" 946890130061"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_170_317-800-170"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 170"," userResponse":" 170"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890142122","data":{"timestamp":" 946890142122"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_267_643-170-267"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 267"," userResponse":" 267"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890153504","data":{"timestamp":" 946890153504"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_317_856-974-317"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 317"," userResponse":" 317"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890165558","data":{"timestamp":" 946890165558"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_485_974-267-485"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 485"," userResponse":" 485"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890176886","data":{"timestamp":" 946890176886"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_557_267-557-170"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 557"," userResponse":" 557"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890190005","data":{"timestamp":" 946890190005"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_643_643-557-800"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 643"," userResponse":" 643"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890200699","data":{"timestamp":" 946890200699"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_800_267-800-557"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 800"," userResponse":" 800"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890210665","data":{"timestamp":" 946890210665"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_856_317-267-856"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 856"," userResponse":" 856"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890232384","data":{"timestamp":" 946890232384"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 974"," userResponse":" 974"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890241771","data":{"timestamp":" 946890241771"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890246132","data":{"timestamp":" 946890246131"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890251230","data":{"timestamp":" 946890251230"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890256532","data":{"timestamp":" 946890256531"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF1_INC_RAND.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890286033","data":{"timestamp":" 946890286033"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890291528","data":{"timestamp":" 946890291527"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890296901","data":{"timestamp":" 946890296900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890303595","data":{"timestamp":" 946890303595"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.s2s.AV.mc.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890318256","data":{"timestamp":" 946890318255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890323992","data":{"timestamp":" 946890323991"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890329387","data":{"timestamp":" 946890329386"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890334630","data":{"timestamp":" 946890334629"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFF1_INC_RAND.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890344086","data":{"timestamp":" 946890344086"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890356883","data":{"timestamp":" 946890356883"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890364556","data":{"timestamp":" 946890364556"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890372857","data":{"timestamp":" 946890372857"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.s2s.AV.mc.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890384322","data":{"timestamp":" 946890384321"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890398095","data":{"timestamp":" 946890398095"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" f53f2a95-c35e-4357-a314-be9a734b4c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.74"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_974_126-267-974"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890407614","data":{"timestamp":" 946890407612"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 4ee7a187-d4eb-44b4-ac92-fecb6ad8e971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890407843","data":{"timestamp":" 946890407843"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 4ee7a187-d4eb-44b4-ac92-fecb6ad8e971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890408452","data":{"timestamp":" 946890408452"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 4ee7a187-d4eb-44b4-ac92-fecb6ad8e971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890408549","data":{"timestamp":" 946890408548"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 4ee7a187-d4eb-44b4-ac92-fecb6ad8e971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890415954","data":{"timestamp":" 946890415953"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 4ee7a187-d4eb-44b4-ac92-fecb6ad8e971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.s2s.AV.mc.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890443983","data":{"timestamp":" 946890443983"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 4ee7a187-d4eb-44b4-ac92-fecb6ad8e971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890449743","data":{"timestamp":" 946890449743"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 4ee7a187-d4eb-44b4-ac92-fecb6ad8e971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890458263","data":{"timestamp":" 946890458262"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 4ee7a187-d4eb-44b4-ac92-fecb6ad8e971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890463801","data":{"timestamp":" 946890463801"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" 4ee7a187-d4eb-44b4-ac92-fecb6ad8e971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890478995","data":{"timestamp":" 946890478995"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890480402","data":{"timestamp":" 946890480402"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890482083","data":{"timestamp":" 946890482082"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890482475","data":{"timestamp":" 946890482475"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890501983","data":{"timestamp":" 946890501983"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890508245","data":{"timestamp":" 946890508245"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890509888","data":{"timestamp":" 946890509888"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890515966","data":{"timestamp":" 946890515966"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890517486","data":{"timestamp":" 946890517486"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890523949","data":{"timestamp":" 946890523949"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890525527","data":{"timestamp":" 946890525527"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890531061","data":{"timestamp":" 946890531061"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890540729","data":{"timestamp":" 946890540729"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890542159","data":{"timestamp":" 946890542159"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890552936","data":{"timestamp":" 946890552936"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_200"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890556263","data":{"timestamp":" 946890556263"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_200"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890562663","data":{"timestamp":" 946890562662"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_200"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890571955","data":{"timestamp":" 946890571955"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_200"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-100s.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890607965","data":{"timestamp":" 946890607965"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_113948"," gameId":" dede0703-42d5-4a4b-85bf-5321bafd1382"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-100s.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_300"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}